So flex direction is the CSS property that's most directly related to the axis.
الاتجاه المرن هو خاصية CSS الأكثر ارتباطًا بالمحور.
When you set the flex direction to be column like this,
وعندما تضبط الاتجاه المرن على عمود هكذا،
it sets the main axis to be the vertical one up and down,
فإنه يضبط المحور الرئيسي رأسيًا من الأعلى والأسفل،
which means the secondary axis will be the horizontal axis across.
وهذا يعني أن المحور الثانوي سيكون المحور الأفقي.
If we just by switching from column to row for our flex direction,
وعند تغيير الاتجاه المرن من عمود إلى صف،
we're also switching which is our main axis which is now going
يتغير المحور الرئيسي ليصبح
horizontally as opposed to our secondary axis which will be the one that is up and down.
أفقيًا، مقابل المحور الثانوي الذي يصبح عموديًا.
These are also going to map one-to-one to justify content and align items,
ستمثل هذه المحاور نقاط ارتباط واحدة مقابل الأخرى لضبط المحتوى ومحاذاة العناصر
which are used to justify or align things based on which axis they are on.
وهو ما يستخدم لضبط أو محاذاة العناصر بناء على المحور الذي تكون عليه.
So depending on whether you have set your flex direction to row or column,
بالتالي، وبناءً على ضبط الاتجاه المرن إلى صف أو عمود،
you'll actually see a line items and justify content
سنلاحظ تغير محاذاة العناصر وضبط المحتوى
interact slightly differently because those and everything
لأنها تتفاعل بشكل مختلف فليلًا نظرًا
else in flex are tied to the relationship of
لارتباط كافة العناصر في فليكس بالعلاقة
these two axis that are initially set using flex direction.
بين هذين المحورين اللذين ضبطناهما من البداية باستخدام الاتجاه المرن.